// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: 'Is marketing the same as advertising ?',
    answer: 'No',
    options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Not Exactly', "I'm indifferent"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: 'What is the full meaning of KPI ?',
    answer: 'Key Performance Indicator',
    options: [
      'Keep Performance Invoice',
      'Key Performance Indicator',
      'Kit Proof Indentation',
      'None of the above',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: 'What does MRR stand for?',
    answer: 'Monthly Recurring Revenue',
    options: [
      'Monthly Revenue Ratio',
      'Market Rational Ratio',
      'Monthly Recurring Revenue',
      'Mix Revenue Ratio',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: 'What does ARR stand for?',
    answer: 'Annual Recurring Revenue',
    options: [
      'Any Rational Ratio',
      'Annual Revenue Ratio',
      'Annual Recurring Revenue',
      'Annual Rationalist Rap',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: 'One of these is not a marketing type?',
    answer: 'Innovative Marketing',
    options: [
      'Social Media Marketing',
      'Innovative Marketing',
      'Email Marketing',
      'Digital Marketing',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: 'When can you say the marketing team has done very well ?',
    answer: 'All of the above',
    options: [
      'Excellent Market Penetration',
      'Reduction in marketing budget with great KPI',
      'Growth In The Public Eye',
      'All of the above',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: 'Closest man to the sun?',
    answer: 'Nel armstrong',
    options: ['Nel armstrong', 'John Dalton', 'Charlse rogers', 'Iron man'],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: 'What is 7 x 7?',
    answer: '49',
    options: ['23', '49', '30', '56'],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: 'Who sang Hardest to love?',
    answer: 'The weekend',
    options: ['The weekend', 'Eminem', 'Don Jazzy', 'Scarlet Gomez'],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: 'When did Nigeria gain Independence?',
    answer: '1960',
    options: ['1960', '1961', '1962', '1963'],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: 'Who wrote the national anthem?',
    answer: 'Taiwo Akinkumi',
    options: [
      'Taiwo Akinkumi',
      'The chosen one',
      'World best',
      'I have no idea',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: 'Who is the father of Counseling?',
    answer: 'Frank Parson',
    options: ['Jack Daniels', 'Frank Parson', 'Calum Scott', 'John Wick'],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: 'Who is the  lady with the highest I.Q?',
    answer: 'Servont',
    options: ['Servont', 'Jane', 'Casper', 'Tunde'],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: 'What country colonized Nigeria?',
    answer: 'Britan',
    options: ['France', 'London', 'Judea', 'Slovakia'],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: 'Who founded NYSC?',
    answer: 'Yakubu Gowon',
    options: [
      'Nnamdi Azikwe',
      'Kikelomo Banjoko',
      'Olusegun Obasanjo',
      'Yakubu Gowon',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: 'Who invented the computer?',
    answer: 'Charlse Babbage',
    options: ['Charlse Babbage', 'John Henry', 'Carl Rogers', 'Ian Lannister'],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: 'What is 2 + 2?',
    answer: '4',
    options: ['13', '14', '15', '4'],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: 'What does RSV mean in the bible?',
    answer: 'Revised Standard Version',
    options: [
      'Rotational Strong view',
      'Revised Standard Version',
      'R S V',
      'Remember Saint Veron',
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: 'Who created heaven and earth',
    answer: 'Almighty God',
    options: ['Almight God', 'Almighty God', 'God', 'God Almighty'],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: 'Who sang Only You?',
    answer: 'Calum Scott',
    options: ['Dj Khaled', 'Calum Scott', 'Beyonce', 'Micheal Jackson'],
  },
];
